# **Brock Chapin**

brockchapin@gmail.com (408) 781-7525

#### **Professional Summary**

Senior level desktop management engineer with experience in Windows, MacOS, and Linux systems at medium-large enterprise environments.

8 years of experience as technical lead for IT operations projects including systems integration, endpoint backup and security, configuration management systems, and migrations.

Solid experience delivering customized reporting and dashboards to drive business decisions. Experience using API scripting, and Azure cloud data sources.

Dedicated to automation and optimization of IT operations tools and processes. Embraces devops culture and tools to shorten delivery times and stabilize environments.

### **Skills & Qualifications**

- Strong skills in shell script and query languages for systems management and reporting including Powershell, Bash, T-SQL, and Power Query/M
- Git and source control experience. Owner of multiple private GitLab projects and repos for scripts and server configuration.
- Skilled JAMF Pro / Casper admin with experience in design, and implementation of onsite infrastructure, and Apple macOS and iOS management and provisioning.
- 8+ years' experience as System Center Configuration Manager (SCCM) and Intune Engineer who can efficiently Implement, Manage, and troubleshoot SCCM, SQL, and SRSS in Enterprise environments.
- 2+ years administering Code42 CrashPlan in hybrid cloud environment for 7000+ clients on Windows, Linux, and macOS.
- Experience building custom compliance dashboards and reporting solutions using Power BI, Excel, Powershell, and SQL
- Strong understanding of Application packaging, Windows Imaging, MDM and Mobile Device Management, Chef Open Source, CentOS, Windows Server, Active Directory, Group Policy, Certificate Management, PKI, and Identity Management, LDAP.

## **Employment History**

Brocade Communications Systems, Inc. (NASDAQ: BRCD)
February 2015 – Present
Job Title – IT Systems Administrator II, Endpoint Engineering

- Implemented JAMF Pro / Casper multi server environment on RedHat Linux with internet facing JSS and JDS.
- Built JAMF DEP based provisioning of macOS and iOS devices (Supervised and BYOD) with Apple Enterprise Connect integration.
- Implemented Microsoft Intune and deployed to 1000 systems as part of Brocade's acquisition of Ruckus Wireless.
- Redesign and upgrade of Code42 CrashPlan PROe endpoint backup solution in a hybrid cloud setup. Deployed to over 7000 windows, macOS, and linux systems.
- Built POC of Chef open source to manage debian linux desktop environment
- SCCM administrator for 6000 clients (windows and linux), multiple site systems, distribution points, and offloaded SQL.
- Managed Office 365 subscription and Azure Active Directory

## Unisys Corporation (NYSE: UIS) March 2011 – February 2015

Job Title: Systems Analyst II - CXF EP Endpoint Global

- **Levi's Stadium Implementation** Spring 2014: worked with City of Santa Clara and the 49ers to implement a new Police Command Center at the stadium.
- Santa Clara Police and Fire Department MDC Project Fall 2013: upgraded the invehicle MDC mobile hardware, RadioIP VPN system, Motorola Dispatch software and GIS mapping systems in all emergency and service vehicles and dispatch center.
- Single Point of Contact and Technical Lead for Endpoint Management Services at City of Santa Clara
- Design and Implementation of SCCM 2007 to SCCM 2012 Migration

**Unisys Corporation (NYSE: UIS)** 

Dec 2009 - Mar 2011

Job Title: UTS - Field Services Lead (City of Santa Clara)

ACS - XEROX (NYSE: XRX) August 2008 — Dec 2009

**Job Title: Government Solutions Desktop Engineer (City of Santa Clara)** 

#### **Education and Professional Certification**

JAMF CCT, CCA

Microsoft MCTS – Administering System Center Configuration Manager 2012

**WWW** 

http://twitter.com/bchap1n

http://www.linkedin.com/in/brockchapin

https://www.jamf.com/jamf-nation/users/41150/bchapin

https://github.com/brizzock